Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: High Adventure with Lowell Thomas (Morocco), 1958 May; 2 (Box 1548)
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 362
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 363
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 364
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 365
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 366
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 367
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 368
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 369
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 370
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 371
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 372
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 373
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 374
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 375
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 376
  - Subject files: High Adventure with Lowell Thomas (Morocco), 1958 May; 3 (Box 1548)
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 1
    - [Various photos from on the sets of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 2
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 3
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 4
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 5
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas filming during his "High Adventure" in Morocco], 6
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 7
    - [Various phtotos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 8
    - [Various photos of Lowell Thomas filming his "High Adventure" in Morocco], 9
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 10
    - [Various photos taken during Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 11
    - [Various photos taken during Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 12
    - [Various photos taken during Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 13
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 14
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 15
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 16
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 17
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 18
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 19
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 20
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 21
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 22
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 23
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 24
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 25
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 26
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 27
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 28
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 29
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 30
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 31
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 32
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 33
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 34
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 35
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 36
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 37
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 38
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 39
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 40
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 41
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 42
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 43
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 44
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 45
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 46
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 47
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 48
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 49
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 50
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 51
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 52
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 53
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 54
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 55
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 56
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 57
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 58
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 59
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 60
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 61
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 62
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 63
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 64
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 65
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 66
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 67
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 68
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 69
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 70
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 71
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 72
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 73
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 74
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 75
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 76
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 77
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 78
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 79
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 80
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 81
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 82
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 83
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 84
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 85
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 86
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 87
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 88
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 89
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 90
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 91
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 92
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 93
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 94
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 95
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 96
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 97
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 98
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 99
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 100
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 101
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 102
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 103
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 104
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 105
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 106
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 107
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 108
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 109
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 110
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 111
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 112
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 113
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 114
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 115
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 116
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 117
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 118
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 119
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 120
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 121
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 122
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 123
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 124
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 125
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 126
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 127
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 128
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 129
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 130
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 131
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 132
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 133
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 134
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 135
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 136
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 137
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 138
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 139
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 140
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 141
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 142
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 143
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 144
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 145
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 146
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 147
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 148
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 149
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 150
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 151
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 152
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 153
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 154
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 155
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 156
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 157
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 158
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 159
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 160
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 161
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 162
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 163
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 164
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 165
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 166
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 167
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 168
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 169
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 170
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 171
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 172
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 173
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 174
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 175
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 176
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 177
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 178
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 179
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 180
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 181
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 182
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 183
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 184
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 185
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 186
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 187
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 188
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 189
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 190
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 191
    - [Various photos from Lowell Thomas's "High Adventure" in Morocco], 192
  - Subject files: High Adventure with Lowell Thomas (Alaska), 1958 October; 4 (Box 1548)
    - LOWELL THOMAS SHOWS ARCTIC GEAR USED IN FILMING ALASKA "HIGH ADVENTURE"; Lowell Thomas displays some foul-weather gear used in filming the Alaska episode of "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas," which will have its premiere Wednesday, Oct. 8, 8:00-9:00 PM, EDT, over the CBS Television Network.; Between air trips, world traveler Thomas pauses at the New York office of Odyssey Productions, Inc., which is filming his overseas adventure episodes, 1
    - Note: [press release] LOWELL THOMAS SHOWS ARCTIC GEAR USED IN FILMING ALASKA "HIGH ADVENTURE"; Lowell Thomas displays some foul-weather gear used in filming the Alaska episode of "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas," which will have its premiere Wednesday, Oct. 8, 8:00-9:00 PM, EDT, over the CBS Television Network.; Between air trips, world traveler Thomas pauses at the New York office of Odyssey Productions, Inc., which is filming his overseas adventure episodes, 2
    - PIQUED BY PEAK -- One of Alaska's imposing mountains is a background for Lowell Thomas as the intrepid explorer-author-producer gets ready to "shoot" scenes in full color for the initial installment of the new "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" TV series which will bow over the CBS television network on Wednesday, October 8th, from 8:00 to 9:00 p.m., Eastern Daylight Time. Entire show is devoted to the challenges and possibilities of America's newest state and last big frontier. "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" is presented by the united Motors System and Delco-Remy Division of General Motors, 3
    - Note: [press release] PIQUED BY PEAK -- One of Alaska's imposing mountains is a background for Lowell Thomas as the intrepid explorer-author-producer gets ready to "shoot" scenes in full color for the initial installment of the new "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" TV series which will bow over the CBS television network on Wednesday, October 8th, from 8:00 to 9:00 p.m., Eastern Daylight Time. Entire show is devoted to the challenges and possibilities of America's newest state and last big frontier. "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" is presented by the united Motors System and Delco-Remy Division of General Motors, 4
    - FAMILY FAREWELL - Leaving on a dangerous camera mission deep in Alaska mountains for scenes in the first episode of the new "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" series (in full color, CBS television network, Wednesday, October 8th, from 8:00 to 9:00 p.m. EDT), Lowell Thomas, Sr. (right) and son, Lowell Thomas, Jr., get go-ahead signal at base headquarters from latter's wife and 3-year old daughter, Ann. Flag is official emblem of the Explorers Club of New York. Presented by the United Motors System and Delco-Remy Division of General Motors, four thrill-packed installments of "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" will be seen during the coming fall and winter, 5
    - Note: [press release] FAMILY FAREWELL - Leaving on a dangerous camera mission deep in Alaska mountains for scenes in the first episode of the new "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" series (in full color, CBS television network, Wednesday, October 8th, from 8:00 to 9:00 p.m. EDT), Lowell Thomas, Sr. (right) and son, Lowell Thomas, Jr., get go-ahead signal at base headquarters from latter's wife and 3-year old daughter, Ann. Flag is official emblem of the Explorers Club of New York. Presented by the United Motors System and Delco-Remy Division of General Motors, four thrill-packed installments of "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" will be seen during the coming fall and winter, 6
    - GETS INSIDE INFO - Chiefs of the Tlingit Indians of Alaska let Lowell Thomas in on age-old secret tribal rites during production of certain scenes for the first episode (Alaska - America's Last Frontier) of the new "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" series in full color on Wednesday, October 8th, from 8:00 to 9:00 p.m., Eastern Daylight Time under the sponsorship of the United Motors System and Delco-Remy Division of General Motors. Before the purchase of Alaska by the United States in 1867, the Tlingits fought a bloody war with the incumbent Russians, 7
    - Note: [press release] GETS INSIDE INFO - Chiefs of the Tlingit Indians of Alaska let Lowell Thomas in on age-old secret tribal rites during production of certain scenes for the first episode (Alaska - America's Last Frontier) of the new "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" series in full color on Wednesday, October 8th, from 8:00 to 9:00 p.m., Eastern Daylight Time under the sponsorship of the United Motors System and Delco-Remy Division of General Motors. Before the purchase of Alaska by the United States in 1867, the Tlingits fought a bloody war with the incumbent Russians, 8
    - LOWELL THOMAS AND HIS SON, LOWELL, JR.; "HIGH ADVENTURE" TEAM TRAVEL TO ALASKA; Lowell Thomas (left) and his son, Lowell, Jr., take a break from filming operations on the Juneau Ice Cap, Alaska, where "High Adventures With Lowell Thomas" will make its debut Wednesday, Oct. 8, 8:00-9:00 PM, EDT, over the CBS Television Network, 9
    - Note: [press release] LOWELL THOMAS AND HIS SON, LOWELL, JR.; "HIGH ADVENTURE" TEAM TRAVEL TO ALASKA; Lowell Thomas (left) and his son, Lowell, Jr., take a break from filming operations on the Juneau Ice Cap, Alaska, where "High Adventures With Lowell Thomas" will make its debut Wednesday, Oct. 8, 8:00-9:00 PM, EDT, over the CBS Television Network, 10
    - ICY INTRODUCTION - Lowell Thomas emerges from a crevasse in Alaska's immense glacial ice pack during "shooting" of first edition of the new series of "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" color films set for showing over the CBS television network Wednesday, October 8th, 8:00 to 9:00 p.m., Eastern Daylight Time. Sun glasses, special skin ointment, etc. are necessary to protect the face and eyes from dangerous infra-red rays bouncing off the glaring snow. Lowell Thomas and camera crews ranged America's newest state from Point Barrow to Juneau for the one-hour Alaskan "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas," which again is presented by the United Motors System and Delco-Remy Division of General Motors, 11
    - Note: [press release] ICY INTRODUCTION - Lowell Thomas emerges from a crevasse in Alaska's immense glacial ice pack during "shooting" of first edition of the new series of "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas" color films set for showing over the CBS television network Wednesday, October 8th, 8:00 to 9:00 p.m., Eastern Daylight Time. Sun glasses, special skin ointment, etc. are necessary to protect the face and eyes from dangerous infra-red rays bouncing off the glaring snow. Lowell Thomas and camera crews ranged America's newest state from Point Barrow to Juneau for the one-hour Alaskan "High Adventure with Lowell Thomas," which again is presented by the United Motors System and Delco-Remy Division of General Motors, 12
    - [press release] LOWELL THOMAS TRECKS TO JUNEAU ICE CAP AS "HIGH ADVENTURE" BOWS OCT. 8; Lowell Thomas visits the rugged terrain of Alaska's Juneau Ice Cap for the seasonal debut of "High Adventure With Lowell Thomas" Wednesday, Oct. 8 8:00-9:00 PM, EDT, over the CBS Television Network. The adventure series will show Alaska as the "last frontier" of the North American continent, 13
    - Note: LOWELL THOMAS TRECKS TO JUNEAU ICE CAP AS "HIGH ADVENTURE" BOWS OCT. 8; Lowell Thomas visits the rugged terrain of Alaska's Juneau Ice Cap for the seasonal debut of "High Adventure With Lowell Thomas" Wednesday, Oct. 8 8:00-9:00 PM, EDT, over the CBS Television Network. The adventure series will show Alaska as the "last frontier" of the North American continent, 14
    - [Lowell Thomas reading a book in his tent in Alaska], 15